DIMITRIS RAMMOS

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Hello, I am 21 years old and I live in Athens. I am a Associate Software Engineer at Wappier. I am a BackEnd Developer and we coding with Rust. I am a undergraduate student in Department of Informatics and Telecommunications, University of Athens. I am at 4th year of studies.

CONTACT



+30 6940870953



jrammos@outlook.com.gr



www.linkedin.com/in/dimitrisrammos/



<u>DimitrisRammos</u>



My portfolio

EDUCATIONS

Department of Informatics and Telecommunications, NKUA

COMPUTER SCIENCE, OCT 2019 - PRESENT



SKILLS

- Rust
- C
- C++
- Java
- MySQL
- Python
- HTML/CSS
- JavaScript
- Git
- Assembly

EXPERIENCE

Check-In Agent

GOLDAIR HANDLING, JUL 2021 - SEP 2021 - HERAKLION, GREECE

I was Check-In Agent for Aegean Airlines

Associate Software Engineer

WAPPIER, AUG 2022 - PRESENT - ATHENS, GREECE I am a Backend developer and I code in Rust.

PROJECTS

- Tic Tac Toe_- Game
- Role Playing Game Terminal Game
- Graph Coloring Project Project
- Artificial-Intelligence Project
- Compilers Project
- My Portfolio My WebPage

LANGUAGES

- Greek Mother Tongue
- English Lower

HOBBIES

Gym -

Box